Jeff Natiuk

Tallahassee, FL

Summary

Senior software consultant with 4 years of professional experience developing in .NET, HTML, Javascript, and SQL on a web (ASP/IIS) platform. I am looking for something to challenge my skill-set and put my degree to deeper use.

Skills

Programming Languages: C#, VB, Java, HTML5/CSS/Javascript, JQuery

Frameworks: ASP.NET, WPF, Dropbox Java libraries IDEs: Visual Studio, NetBeans, Eclipse, Android Studio Version Control Systems: Team Foundation Server, GitHub

Databases: Microsoft SQL, MySQL

Operating Systems: Windows, Ubuntu, Unix

Projects

- **Udacity Android Nanodegree Apps** WIP Apps from <u>Udacity</u> Curriculum.
- Personal Finance Application Created in C# WPF, pulls Chase Credit Card statement data dynamically using <u>Selenium</u> to provide spending category-based budget views. Inspired by <u>Mint</u> and <u>BillGuard</u>.

Work Experience

Sogeti USA LLC - Tallahassee, FL

09/2011 - Present

Senior Software Consultant - Florida Dept. of Education

05/2012 - Present

- Maintaining and creating new pages for an existing web application written in VB.NET and MS SQL that serves an average of 250,000 page hits per day.
- Performing DBA duties to improve SQL efficiency in the app (clustered vs non-clustered index optimization, SQL Server Profiler).
- Participating in a Scrum life cycle for project planning/development.
- Trained one new college hire and two new consultants with the application as they were onboarded.

Software Consultant - Florida Department of Revenue

09/2011 - 05/2012

- Produced a new web application with a new offline component desktop application as part of a C# development team.
- Responsible for developing the offline application (C# with WPF) and the custom visual style of the SharePoint-based Florida Revenue Law Library.
- Created a process using <u>Sikuli</u> to automate the generation of PostScript printing format files on a page by page basis from Adobe InDesign.

Freelance Development - Tallahassee, FL

08/2012 - 07/2013

Software Consultant - Nightlife Unleashed

- Built Java-based tools for to enhance naming convention integrity and manage thousands of photos within a Dropbox file system using the Java Dropbox API.
- Executed from a Linux server using cron jobs to schedule execution.

Education

Undergraduate:Florida State University - BS Computer Science08/2007 - 08/2011Nanodegree:Udacity Android Developer06/2015 - Present (In Progress)Certification:Microsoft 70-480 - Programming in HTML5 with JS and CSS301/2013

Interests

Guitar, Video Games, Streaming on Twitch, Reading, Craft Beer